Guess who's coming back to radio?
Did you miss me?
That's right, y'all.
Amanda Seals, yours truly, is back on the air.
You can catch me every Friday, 12 to 2 Pacific and 4 to 6 Pacific,
on Tavis Smiley's KVLA Talk 1580 Radio.
I'll be bringing y'all some Black Red News, telling you how Black I feel today.
We'll do some critical thinking exercises.
And, of course, I will hit you with a public Seals announcement, the PSA.
So if you want to listen to me doing what I do, talking my talk and saying my thing,
make sure you download the KVLA 1580 Talk Radio app so that you can check in and check me out.
The summer of Seals is here!
They keep trying to get rid of me, but you can't.